Attention! There are numerous fake websites, email addresses and social media accounts
requesting or encouraging for donations in the name of The SCOAN, T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV.
They may claim to be collecting funds to build a SCOAN worship centre,
bible college or orphanage in their respective countries.
Others also solicit funds for spiritual items to be sent out.
They are fraudsters!
There is currently no plan to build or acquire SCOAN premises worldwide.
Don't let anyone deceive you.
For donations: God has a way of speaking to the hearts of His people for our needs.
We never send anyone and can never send anyone.
If we need you (partners), we have a way of reaching you, through Emmanuel TV - which is our mouthpiece.
Following are just a few examples out of thousands of fraulent announcements.
FAKE